{
  "id": "da-de-mix-pack-01",
  "name": "Dänisch ↔ Deutsch – Mix Pack 01 (500)",
  "src": "DA/DE",
  "tgt": "DE/DA",
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "hud",
      "back": "haut"
    },
    {
      "front": "peberfrugt",
      "back": "paprika"
    },
    {
      "front": "butik",
      "back": "laden"
    },
    {
      "front": "rød",
      "back": "rot"
    },
    {
      "front": "was",
      "back": "hvad"
    },
    {
      "front": "wie",
      "back": "hvordan"
    },
    {
      "front": "arbeiten",
      "back": "arbejde"
    },
    {
      "front": "mandag",
      "back": "montag"
    },
    {
      "front": "tablet",
      "back": "tablet"
    },
    {
      "front": "læge",
      "back": "arzt"
    },
    {
      "front": "november",
      "back": "november"
    },
    {
      "front": "ti",
      "back": "zehn"
    },
    {
      "front": "bedstefar",
      "back": "großvater"
    },
    {
      "front": "dass",
      "back": "at"
    },
    {
      "front": "kaffe",
      "back": "kaffee"
    },
    {
      "front": "sitzplatz",
      "back": "sæde"
    },
    {
      "front": "mobil",
      "back": "handy"
    },
    {
      "front": "forsinkelse",
      "back": "verspätung"
    },
    {
      "front": "ingeniør",
      "back": "ingenieur"
    },
    {
      "front": "dreizehn",
      "back": "tretten"
    },
    {
      "front": "sofa",
      "back": "sofa"
    },
    {
      "front": "to",
      "back": "zwei"
    },
    {
      "front": "blyant",
      "back": "bleistift"
    },
    {
      "front": "billig",
      "back": "billig"
    },
    {
      "front": "tirsdag",
      "back": "dienstag"
    },
    {
      "front": "bagved",
      "back": "hinten"
    },
    {
      "front": "ameise",
      "back": "myre"
    },
    {
      "front": "hane",
      "back": "hahn"
    },
    {
      "front": "unten",
      "back": "nede"
    },
    {
      "front": "ente",
      "back": "and"
    },
    {
      "front": "eins",
      "back": "en"
    },
    {
      "front": "ihr",
      "back": "i"
    },
    {
      "front": "öl",
      "back": "olie"
    },
    {
      "front": "fjern",
      "back": "weit"
    },
    {
      "front": "aprikose",
      "back": "abrikos"
    },
    {
      "front": "außen",
      "back": "udenfor"
    },
    {
      "front": "pfanne",
      "back": "pande"
    },
    {
      "front": "lautsprecher",
      "back": "højttaler"
    },
    {
      "front": "journalist",
      "back": "journalist"
    },
    {
      "front": "skrive",
      "back": "schreiben"
    },
    {
      "front": "zug",
      "back": "tog"
    },
    {
      "front": "kold",
      "back": "kalt"
    },
    {
      "front": "künstler",
      "back": "kunstner"
    },
    {
      "front": "tre",
      "back": "drei"
    },
    {
      "front": "himmel",
      "back": "himmel"
    },
    {
      "front": "datter",
      "back": "tochter"
    },
    {
      "front": "schwierig",
      "back": "svær"
    },
    {
      "front": "bjørn",
      "back": "bär"
    },
    {
      "front": "brot",
      "back": "brød"
    },
    {
      "front": "tante",
      "back": "tante"
    },
    {
      "front": "apfel",
      "back": "æble"
    },
    {
      "front": "vind",
      "back": "wind"
    },
    {
      "front": "fire",
      "back": "vier"
    },
    {
      "front": "bedstemor",
      "back": "großmutter"
    },
    {
      "front": "nahe",
      "back": "nær"
    },
    {
      "front": "øjne",
      "back": "augen"
    },
    {
      "front": "pen",
      "back": "stift"
    },
    {
      "front": "køreplan",
      "back": "fahrplan"
    },
    {
      "front": "mai",
      "back": "maj"
    },
    {
      "front": "meer",
      "back": "hav"
    },
    {
      "front": "zitrone",
      "back": "citron"
    },
    {
      "front": "fordi",
      "back": "weil"
    },
    {
      "front": "mantel",
      "back": "frakke"
    },
    {
      "front": "machen",
      "back": "lave"
    },
    {
      "front": "fußball",
      "back": "fodbold"
    },
    {
      "front": "blume",
      "back": "blomst"
    },
    {
      "front": "fisk",
      "back": "fisch"
    },
    {
      "front": "cykling",
      "back": "radfahren"
    },
    {
      "front": "din",
      "back": "dein"
    },
    {
      "front": "supermarked",
      "back": "supermarkt"
    },
    {
      "front": "beskidt",
      "back": "schmutzig"
    },
    {
      "front": "kommen",
      "back": "komme"
    },
    {
      "front": "lav",
      "back": "leise"
    },
    {
      "front": "bomuld",
      "back": "baumwolle"
    },
    {
      "front": "wolle",
      "back": "uld"
    },
    {
      "front": "forstå",
      "back": "verstehen"
    },
    {
      "front": "kopfhörer",
      "back": "hovedtelefoner"
    },
    {
      "front": "drikkepenge",
      "back": "trinkgeld"
    },
    {
      "front": "freitag",
      "back": "fredag"
    },
    {
      "front": "welche (pl.)",
      "back": "hvilke"
    },
    {
      "front": "hvorfor",
      "back": "warum"
    },
    {
      "front": "ur",
      "back": "uhr"
    },
    {
      "front": "være",
      "back": "sein"
    },
    {
      "front": "koffer",
      "back": "kuffert"
    },
    {
      "front": "skildpadde",
      "back": "schildkröte"
    },
    {
      "front": "mappe",
      "back": "mappe"
    },
    {
      "front": "og",
      "back": "und"
    },
    {
      "front": "haltestelle",
      "back": "stoppested"
    },
    {
      "front": "brief",
      "back": "brev"
    },
    {
      "front": "banane",
      "back": "banan"
    },
    {
      "front": "café",
      "back": "café"
    },
    {
      "front": "svamp",
      "back": "pilz"
    },
    {
      "front": "nem",
      "back": "einfach"
    },
    {
      "front": "laut",
      "back": "høj"
    },
    {
      "front": "stern",
      "back": "stjerne"
    },
    {
      "front": "schule",
      "back": "skole"
    },
    {
      "front": "bauch",
      "back": "mave"
    },
    {
      "front": "schuh",
      "back": "sko"
    },
    {
      "front": "teater",
      "back": "theater"
    },
    {
      "front": "bælte",
      "back": "gürtel"
    },
    {
      "front": "taxi",
      "back": "taxa"
    },
    {
      "front": "lørdag",
      "back": "samstag"
    },
    {
      "front": "bord",
      "back": "tisch"
    },
    {
      "front": "hånd",
      "back": "hand"
    },
    {
      "front": "forkølelse",
      "back": "schnupfen"
    },
    {
      "front": "jacke",
      "back": "jakke"
    },
    {
      "front": "lime",
      "back": "limette"
    },
    {
      "front": "kleid",
      "back": "kjole"
    },
    {
      "front": "freude",
      "back": "glæde"
    },
    {
      "front": "gryde",
      "back": "topf"
    },
    {
      "front": "rechteck",
      "back": "rektangel"
    },
    {
      "front": "torden",
      "back": "donner"
    },
    {
      "front": "cykel",
      "back": "fahrrad"
    },
    {
      "front": "krabbe",
      "back": "krabbe"
    },
    {
      "front": "bild",
      "back": "billede"
    },
    {
      "front": "bog",
      "back": "buch"
    },
    {
      "front": "bjerg",
      "back": "berg"
    },
    {
      "front": "durstig",
      "back": "tørstig"
    },
    {
      "front": "ringbind",
      "back": "ordner"
    },
    {
      "front": "pause",
      "back": "pause"
    },
    {
      "front": "ben",
      "back": "bein"
    },
    {
      "front": "klein",
      "back": "lille"
    },
    {
      "front": "fjernsyn",
      "back": "fernseher"
    },
    {
      "front": "restaurant",
      "back": "restaurant"
    },
    {
      "front": "grim",
      "back": "hässlich"
    },
    {
      "front": "pære",
      "back": "birne"
    },
    {
      "front": "køkken",
      "back": "küche"
    },
    {
      "front": "programmør",
      "back": "programmierer"
    },
    {
      "front": "nul",
      "back": "null"
    },
    {
      "front": "neu",
      "back": "ny"
    },
    {
      "front": "ferien",
      "back": "ferie"
    },
    {
      "front": "elev",
      "back": "schüler"
    },
    {
      "front": "ske",
      "back": "löffel"
    },
    {
      "front": "landmand",
      "back": "bauer"
    },
    {
      "front": "eichhörnchen",
      "back": "egern"
    },
    {
      "front": "sorg",
      "back": "trauer"
    },
    {
      "front": "hase",
      "back": "hare"
    },
    {
      "front": "te",
      "back": "tee"
    },
    {
      "front": "tand",
      "back": "zahn"
    },
    {
      "front": "tallerken",
      "back": "teller"
    },
    {
      "front": "gå",
      "back": "gehen"
    },
    {
      "front": "angst",
      "back": "angst"
    },
    {
      "front": "arm",
      "back": "arm"
    },
    {
      "front": "knoblauch",
      "back": "hvidløg"
    },
    {
      "front": "lim",
      "back": "kleber"
    },
    {
      "front": "weiß",
      "back": "hvid"
    },
    {
      "front": "september",
      "back": "september"
    },
    {
      "front": "sø",
      "back": "see"
    },
    {
      "front": "werden",
      "back": "blive"
    },
    {
      "front": "mus",
      "back": "maus"
    },
    {
      "front": "mund",
      "back": "mund"
    },
    {
      "front": "kat",
      "back": "katze"
    },
    {
      "front": "aftale",
      "back": "termin"
    },
    {
      "front": "kartoffel",
      "back": "kartoffel"
    },
    {
      "front": "arbejde",
      "back": "arbeit"
    },
    {
      "front": "hans",
      "back": "seine"
    },
    {
      "front": "gabel",
      "back": "gaffel"
    },
    {
      "front": "læge",
      "back": "arztin"
    },
    {
      "front": "decke",
      "back": "tæppe"
    },
    {
      "front": "krankenhaus",
      "back": "hospital"
    },
    {
      "front": "bahnsteig",
      "back": "perron"
    },
    {
      "front": "hendes",
      "back": "ihre"
    },
    {
      "front": "bildschirm",
      "back": "skærm"
    },
    {
      "front": "salz",
      "back": "salt"
    },
    {
      "front": "sne",
      "back": "schnee"
    },
    {
      "front": "geben",
      "back": "give"
    },
    {
      "front": "ged",
      "back": "ziege"
    },
    {
      "front": "søndag",
      "back": "sonntag"
    },
    {
      "front": "metall",
      "back": "metal"
    },
    {
      "front": "vorn",
      "back": "foran"
    },
    {
      "front": "kartofler",
      "back": "kartoffeln"
    },
    {
      "front": "smerte",
      "back": "schmerz"
    },
    {
      "front": "politibetjent",
      "back": "polizist"
    },
    {
      "front": "de",
      "back": "sie (pl.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "foto",
      "back": "foto"
    },
    {
      "front": "aber",
      "back": "men"
    },
    {
      "front": "sport",
      "back": "sport"
    },
    {
      "front": "gitarre",
      "back": "guitar"
    },
    {
      "front": "meine",
      "back": "min"
    },
    {
      "front": "bus",
      "back": "bus"
    },
    {
      "front": "schnell",
      "back": "hurtig"
    },
    {
      "front": "flugzeug",
      "back": "fly"
    },
    {
      "front": "trafiklys",
      "back": "ampel"
    },
    {
      "front": "visum",
      "back": "visum"
    },
    {
      "front": "lukke",
      "back": "schließen"
    },
    {
      "front": "bäckerei",
      "back": "bager"
    },
    {
      "front": "salat",
      "back": "salat"
    },
    {
      "front": "schere",
      "back": "saks"
    },
    {
      "front": "hände",
      "back": "hænder"
    },
    {
      "front": "krokodil",
      "back": "krokodille"
    },
    {
      "front": "alt",
      "back": "gammel"
    },
    {
      "front": "sprechen",
      "back": "tale"
    },
    {
      "front": "lampe",
      "back": "lampe"
    },
    {
      "front": "verkäufer",
      "back": "sælger"
    },
    {
      "front": "vorhang",
      "back": "gardin"
    },
    {
      "front": "tæppe",
      "back": "teppich"
    },
    {
      "front": "fahrer",
      "back": "chauffør"
    },
    {
      "front": "svømning",
      "back": "schwimmen"
    },
    {
      "front": "pude",
      "back": "kissen"
    },
    {
      "front": "ankunft",
      "back": "ankomst"
    },
    {
      "front": "trauben",
      "back": "druer"
    },
    {
      "front": "regen",
      "back": "regn"
    },
    {
      "front": "fod",
      "back": "fuß"
    },
    {
      "front": "zwiebel",
      "back": "løg"
    },
    {
      "front": "søster",
      "back": "schwester"
    },
    {
      "front": "torv",
      "back": "platz"
    },
    {
      "front": "zucker",
      "back": "sukker"
    },
    {
      "front": "stein",
      "back": "sten"
    },
    {
      "front": "slutte",
      "back": "enden"
    },
    {
      "front": "får",
      "back": "schaf"
    },
    {
      "front": "oben",
      "back": "oppe"
    },
    {
      "front": "vrede",
      "back": "wut"
    },
    {
      "front": "mor",
      "back": "mutter"
    },
    {
      "front": "besteck",
      "back": "bestik"
    },
    {
      "front": "suppe",
      "back": "suppe"
    },
    {
      "front": "plastik",
      "back": "kunststoff"
    },
    {
      "front": "achtzehn",
      "back": "atten"
    },
    {
      "front": "grün",
      "back": "grøn"
    },
    {
      "front": "fluss",
      "back": "flod"
    },
    {
      "front": "musiker",
      "back": "musiker"
    },
    {
      "front": "park",
      "back": "park"
    },
    {
      "front": "jakkesæt",
      "back": "anzug"
    },
    {
      "front": "smør",
      "back": "butter"
    },
    {
      "front": "strand",
      "back": "strand"
    },
    {
      "front": "schokolade",
      "back": "chokolade"
    },
    {
      "front": "huhn",
      "back": "høne"
    },
    {
      "front": "fünfzehn",
      "back": "femten"
    },
    {
      "front": "kærlighed",
      "back": "liebe"
    },
    {
      "front": "dreieck",
      "back": "trekant"
    },
    {
      "front": "have",
      "back": "haben"
    },
    {
      "front": "strømpe",
      "back": "socke"
    },
    {
      "front": "hähnchen",
      "back": "kylling"
    },
    {
      "front": "kontor",
      "back": "büro"
    },
    {
      "front": "forfatter",
      "back": "schriftsteller"
    },
    {
      "front": "quadrat",
      "back": "kvadrat"
    },
    {
      "front": "læse",
      "back": "lesen"
    },
    {
      "front": "prüfung",
      "back": "eksamen"
    },
    {
      "front": "schiff",
      "back": "skib"
    },
    {
      "front": "turkis",
      "back": "türkis"
    },
    {
      "front": "neid",
      "back": "misundelse"
    },
    {
      "front": "spielen",
      "back": "spille"
    },
    {
      "front": "nøgle",
      "back": "schlüssel"
    },
    {
      "front": "togbillet",
      "back": "bahnticket"
    },
    {
      "front": "email",
      "back": "e-mail"
    },
    {
      "front": "aufgabe",
      "back": "opgave"
    },
    {
      "front": "insel",
      "back": "ø"
    },
    {
      "front": "sie",
      "back": "hun"
    },
    {
      "front": "umschlag",
      "back": "kuvert"
    },
    {
      "front": "juni",
      "back": "juni"
    },
    {
      "front": "hut",
      "back": "hat"
    },
    {
      "front": "sauber",
      "back": "ren"
    },
    {
      "front": "december",
      "back": "dezember"
    },
    {
      "front": "glas",
      "back": "glas"
    },
    {
      "front": "svare",
      "back": "antworten"
    },
    {
      "front": "sygdom",
      "back": "krankheit"
    },
    {
      "front": "juli",
      "back": "juli"
    },
    {
      "front": "tomate",
      "back": "tomat"
    },
    {
      "front": "kino",
      "back": "biograf"
    },
    {
      "front": "skov",
      "back": "wald"
    },
    {
      "front": "kort",
      "back": "karte"
    },
    {
      "front": "kort",
      "back": "karten"
    },
    {
      "front": "børn",
      "back": "kinder"
    },
    {
      "front": "frø",
      "back": "frosch"
    },
    {
      "front": "radiergummi",
      "back": "viskelæder"
    },
    {
      "front": "dig",
      "back": "dich"
    },
    {
      "front": "sechzehn",
      "back": "seksten"
    },
    {
      "front": "ham",
      "back": "ihn"
    },
    {
      "front": "barn",
      "back": "kind"
    },
    {
      "front": "stor",
      "back": "groß"
    },
    {
      "front": "nitten",
      "back": "neunzehn"
    },
    {
      "front": "blomkål",
      "back": "blumenkohl"
    },
    {
      "front": "film",
      "back": "film"
    },
    {
      "front": "stof",
      "back": "stoff"
    },
    {
      "front": "håndbold",
      "back": "handball"
    },
    {
      "front": "wandern",
      "back": "vandring"
    },
    {
      "front": "computer",
      "back": "computer"
    },
    {
      "front": "rücken",
      "back": "ryg"
    },
    {
      "front": "broccoli",
      "back": "brokkoli"
    },
    {
      "front": "receptionist",
      "back": "rezeptionist"
    },
    {
      "front": "spørge",
      "back": "fragen"
    },
    {
      "front": "cirkel",
      "back": "kreis"
    },
    {
      "front": "gelb",
      "back": "gul"
    },
    {
      "front": "seng",
      "back": "bett"
    },
    {
      "front": "blau",
      "back": "blå"
    },
    {
      "front": "kaufen",
      "back": "købe"
    },
    {
      "front": "ich",
      "back": "jeg"
    },
    {
      "front": "stolz",
      "back": "stolthed"
    },
    {
      "front": "lufthavn",
      "back": "flughafen"
    },
    {
      "front": "juice",
      "back": "saft"
    },
    {
      "front": "lila",
      "back": "lilla"
    },
    {
      "front": "april",
      "back": "april"
    },
    {
      "front": "langsam",
      "back": "langsom"
    },
    {
      "front": "spiel",
      "back": "spil"
    },
    {
      "front": "gris",
      "back": "schwein"
    },
    {
      "front": "bukser",
      "back": "hose"
    },
    {
      "front": "klima",
      "back": "klima"
    },
    {
      "front": "slips",
      "back": "krawatte"
    },
    {
      "front": "pinguin",
      "back": "pingvin"
    },
    {
      "front": "hai",
      "back": "haj"
    },
    {
      "front": "nøglekort",
      "back": "zimmerkarte"
    },
    {
      "front": "bäcker",
      "back": "bager"
    },
    {
      "front": "elefant",
      "back": "elefant"
    },
    {
      "front": "messer",
      "back": "kniv"
    },
    {
      "front": "zimmer",
      "back": "værelse"
    },
    {
      "front": "hvilket",
      "back": "welches"
    },
    {
      "front": "spiegel",
      "back": "spejl"
    },
    {
      "front": "kopf",
      "back": "hoved"
    },
    {
      "front": "braun",
      "back": "brun"
    },
    {
      "front": "rechnung",
      "back": "regning"
    },
    {
      "front": "deres",
      "back": "ihr (poss.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "pasta",
      "back": "nudeln"
    },
    {
      "front": "reis",
      "back": "ris"
    },
    {
      "front": "august",
      "back": "august"
    },
    {
      "front": "ananas",
      "back": "ananas"
    },
    {
      "front": "kellner",
      "back": "tjener"
    },
    {
      "front": "verband",
      "back": "bandage"
    },
    {
      "front": "heft",
      "back": "hæfte"
    },
    {
      "front": "schauspieler",
      "back": "skuespiller"
    },
    {
      "front": "du",
      "back": "du"
    },
    {
      "front": "ohren",
      "back": "ører"
    },
    {
      "front": "mond",
      "back": "måne"
    },
    {
      "front": "medikament",
      "back": "medicin"
    },
    {
      "front": "vejrudsigten",
      "back": "vorhersage"
    },
    {
      "front": "printer",
      "back": "drucker"
    },
    {
      "front": "det",
      "back": "es"
    },
    {
      "front": "onkel",
      "back": "onkel"
    },
    {
      "front": "rechts",
      "back": "højre"
    },
    {
      "front": "vand",
      "back": "wasser"
    },
    {
      "front": "kød",
      "back": "fleisch"
    },
    {
      "front": "indenfor",
      "back": "innen"
    },
    {
      "front": "friseur",
      "back": "frisør"
    },
    {
      "front": "bønne",
      "back": "bohne"
    },
    {
      "front": "hjælpe",
      "back": "helfen"
    },
    {
      "front": "universitet",
      "back": "universität"
    },
    {
      "front": "forsikring",
      "back": "versicherung"
    },
    {
      "front": "søn",
      "back": "sohn"
    },
    {
      "front": "far",
      "back": "vater"
    },
    {
      "front": "nebel",
      "back": "tåge"
    },
    {
      "front": "schrank",
      "back": "skab"
    },
    {
      "front": "schlafen",
      "back": "sove"
    },
    {
      "front": "qualle",
      "back": "vandmand"
    },
    {
      "front": "essen",
      "back": "spise"
    },
    {
      "front": "zähne",
      "back": "tænder"
    },
    {
      "front": "uns",
      "back": "os"
    },
    {
      "front": "gut",
      "back": "god"
    },
    {
      "front": "ært",
      "back": "erbse"
    },
    {
      "front": "finde",
      "back": "finden"
    },
    {
      "front": "ville",
      "back": "wollen"
    },
    {
      "front": "feber",
      "back": "fieber"
    },
    {
      "front": "sonne",
      "back": "sol"
    },
    {
      "front": "rejse",
      "back": "reise"
    },
    {
      "front": "kamera",
      "back": "kamera"
    },
    {
      "front": "auge",
      "back": "øje"
    },
    {
      "front": "hvem",
      "back": "wer"
    },
    {
      "front": "plaster",
      "back": "pflaster"
    },
    {
      "front": "schach",
      "back": "skak"
    },
    {
      "front": "zwanzig",
      "back": "tyve"
    },
    {
      "front": "sechs",
      "back": "seks"
    },
    {
      "front": "mittwoch",
      "back": "onsdag"
    },
    {
      "front": "lernen",
      "back": "lære"
    },
    {
      "front": "gäste",
      "back": "gæster"
    },
    {
      "front": "forældre",
      "back": "eltern"
    },
    {
      "front": "brandmand",
      "back": "feuerwehrmann"
    },
    {
      "front": "kirsebær",
      "back": "kirsche"
    },
    {
      "front": "handschuh",
      "back": "handske"
    },
    {
      "front": "tiger",
      "back": "tiger"
    },
    {
      "front": "tolv",
      "back": "zwölf"
    },
    {
      "front": "læder",
      "back": "leder"
    },
    {
      "front": "drikke",
      "back": "trinken"
    },
    {
      "front": "studerende",
      "back": "student"
    },
    {
      "front": "affe",
      "back": "abe"
    },
    {
      "front": "lejlighed",
      "back": "wohnung"
    },
    {
      "front": "beginnen",
      "back": "begynde"
    },
    {
      "front": "sturm",
      "back": "storm"
    },
    {
      "front": "temperatur",
      "back": "temperatur"
    },
    {
      "front": "hue",
      "back": "mütze"
    },
    {
      "front": "seemann",
      "back": "sømand"
    },
    {
      "front": "han",
      "back": "er"
    },
    {
      "front": "fødder",
      "back": "füße"
    },
    {
      "front": "müde",
      "back": "træt"
    },
    {
      "front": "musik",
      "back": "musik"
    },
    {
      "front": "cousin",
      "back": "fætter"
    },
    {
      "front": "marts",
      "back": "märz"
    },
    {
      "front": "hjerte",
      "back": "herz"
    },
    {
      "front": "oktober",
      "back": "oktober"
    },
    {
      "front": "pilot",
      "back": "pilot"
    },
    {
      "front": "nehmen",
      "back": "tage"
    },
    {
      "front": "pas",
      "back": "reisepass"
    },
    {
      "front": "overraskelse",
      "back": "überraschung"
    },
    {
      "front": "können",
      "back": "kunne"
    },
    {
      "front": "januar",
      "back": "januar"
    },
    {
      "front": "hende",
      "back": "sie (akk.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "forsker",
      "back": "wissenschaftler"
    },
    {
      "front": "mig",
      "back": "mich"
    },
    {
      "front": "ankunftszeit",
      "back": "ankomsttid"
    },
    {
      "front": "gurke",
      "back": "agurk"
    },
    {
      "front": "schwarz",
      "back": "sort"
    },
    {
      "front": "suchen",
      "back": "lede"
    },
    {
      "front": "abfahrt",
      "back": "afgang"
    },
    {
      "front": "hals",
      "back": "hals"
    },
    {
      "front": "fem",
      "back": "fünf"
    },
    {
      "front": "fersken",
      "back": "pfirsich"
    },
    {
      "front": "krankenschwester",
      "back": "sygeplejerske"
    },
    {
      "front": "nederdel",
      "back": "rock"
    },
    {
      "front": "internet",
      "back": "internet"
    },
    {
      "front": "grau",
      "back": "grå"
    },
    {
      "front": "hvornår",
      "back": "wann"
    },
    {
      "front": "jeres",
      "back": "euer"
    },
    {
      "front": "gras",
      "back": "græs"
    },
    {
      "front": "baum",
      "back": "træ"
    },
    {
      "front": "serviette",
      "back": "serviet"
    },
    {
      "front": "gangplatz",
      "back": "gangplads"
    },
    {
      "front": "vogel",
      "back": "fugl"
    },
    {
      "front": "mechaniker",
      "back": "mekaniker"
    },
    {
      "front": "vierzehn",
      "back": "fjorten"
    },
    {
      "front": "pflaume",
      "back": "blomme"
    },
    {
      "front": "cousine",
      "back": "kusine"
    },
    {
      "front": "heiß",
      "back": "varm"
    },
    {
      "front": "klavier",
      "back": "klaver"
    },
    {
      "front": "wir",
      "back": "vi"
    },
    {
      "front": "løve",
      "back": "löwe"
    },
    {
      "front": "telefon",
      "back": "telefon"
    },
    {
      "front": "sulten",
      "back": "hungrig"
    },
    {
      "front": "februar",
      "back": "februar"
    },
    {
      "front": "bruder",
      "back": "bror"
    },
    {
      "front": "schuhe",
      "back": "sko"
    },
    {
      "front": "hoste",
      "back": "husten"
    },
    {
      "front": "sommerfugl",
      "back": "schmetterling"
    },
    {
      "front": "pfeffer",
      "back": "peber"
    },
    {
      "front": "wein",
      "back": "vin"
    },
    {
      "front": "erdbeere",
      "back": "jordbær"
    },
    {
      "front": "laufen",
      "back": "løb"
    },
    {
      "front": "afgangstid",
      "back": "abfahrtszeit"
    },
    {
      "front": "mælk",
      "back": "milch"
    },
    {
      "front": "scham",
      "back": "skam"
    },
    {
      "front": "arkitekt",
      "back": "architekt"
    },
    {
      "front": "badeværelse",
      "back": "bad"
    },
    {
      "front": "museum",
      "back": "museum"
    },
    {
      "front": "gewit­ter",
      "back": "tordenvejr"
    },
    {
      "front": "rosa",
      "back": "lyserød"
    },
    {
      "front": "socken",
      "back": "strømper"
    },
    {
      "front": "billet",
      "back": "ticket"
    },
    {
      "front": "unser",
      "back": "vores"
    },
    {
      "front": "kreuzung",
      "back": "kryds"
    },
    {
      "front": "verkaufen",
      "back": "sælge"
    },
    {
      "front": "dyr",
      "back": "teuer"
    },
    {
      "front": "køre",
      "back": "fahren"
    },
    {
      "front": "delfin",
      "back": "delfin"
    },
    {
      "front": "tastatur",
      "back": "tastatur"
    },
    {
      "front": "holz",
      "back": "træ"
    },
    {
      "front": "euch",
      "back": "jer"
    },
    {
      "front": "vejr",
      "back": "wetter"
    },
    {
      "front": "warm",
      "back": "varm"
    },
    {
      "front": "dans",
      "back": "tanzen"
    },
    {
      "front": "tennis",
      "back": "tennis"
    },
    {
      "front": "oder",
      "back": "eller"
    },
    {
      "front": "lied",
      "back": "sang"
    },
    {
      "front": "recept",
      "back": "rezept"
    },
    {
      "front": "overstregningstusch",
      "back": "markierer"
    },
    {
      "front": "notizbuch",
      "back": "notesbog"
    },
    {
      "front": "siebzehn",
      "back": "sytten"
    },
    {
      "front": "vigtig",
      "back": "wichtig"
    },
    {
      "front": "spinat",
      "back": "spinat"
    },
    {
      "front": "schlecht",
      "back": "dårlig"
    },
    {
      "front": "kalender",
      "back": "kalender"
    },
    {
      "front": "wolf",
      "back": "ulv"
    },
    {
      "front": "kop",
      "back": "tasse"
    },
    {
      "front": "sieben",
      "back": "syv"
    },
    {
      "front": "welcher",
      "back": "hvilken"
    },
    {
      "front": "øl",
      "back": "bier"
    },
    {
      "front": "ohr",
      "back": "øre"
    },
    {
      "front": "banegård",
      "back": "bahnhof"
    },
    {
      "front": "fensterplatz",
      "back": "vinduesplads"
    },
    {
      "front": "acht",
      "back": "otte"
    },
    {
      "front": "haus",
      "back": "hus"
    },
    {
      "front": "stol",
      "back": "stuhl"
    },
    {
      "front": "öffnen",
      "back": "åbne"
    },
    {
      "front": "koch",
      "back": "kok"
    },
    {
      "front": "wal",
      "back": "hval"
    },
    {
      "front": "bil",
      "back": "auto"
    },
    {
      "front": "hemd",
      "back": "skjorte"
    },
    {
      "front": "had",
      "back": "hass"
    },
    {
      "front": "sie (obj.)",
      "back": "dem"
    },
    {
      "front": "lineal",
      "back": "lineal"
    },
    {
      "front": "reservation",
      "back": "reservierung"
    },
    {
      "front": "mango",
      "back": "mango"
    },
    {
      "front": "empfang",
      "back": "reception"
    },
    {
      "front": "hund",
      "back": "hund"
    },
    {
      "front": "tafel",
      "back": "tavle"
    },
    {
      "front": "sehen",
      "back": "se"
    },
    {
      "front": "lærer",
      "back": "lehrer"
    },
    {
      "front": "schön",
      "back": "smuk"
    },
    {
      "front": "hotel",
      "back": "hotel"
    },
    {
      "front": "lyn",
      "back": "blitz"
    },
    {
      "front": "papier",
      "back": "papir"
    },
    {
      "front": "elf",
      "back": "elleve"
    },
    {
      "front": "mais",
      "back": "majs"
    },
    {
      "front": "pferd",
      "back": "hest"
    },
    {
      "front": "donnerstag",
      "back": "torsdag"
    },
    {
      "front": "ni",
      "back": "neun"
    }
  ]
}